postcodeanywhere.co.uk 2018-05-19

# PCA Predict Privacy Policy

## Privacy & Security Policy

The purpose of this document is to bring to your attention GB Group plc's (trading as “PCA” or “PCA Predict”) policy regarding the use of, and protection of, personal data stored on our systems. It also explains how we use the information we collect about you, how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy.

In accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, GB Group plc is registered as a 'Data Controller' on the public Register of Data Controllers as maintained by the UK’s Information Commissioner. When you use this website, please bear in mind that we may record: 

  * the areas of the website that you visit; and
  * information about your computer, such as which browser you are using, your network location, the type of connection you are using (e.g. broadband, ADSL etc.) and your IP address.

We do this by using cookies and tags. See our Cookies Policy www.pcapredict.com/cookies for more information on what a cookie is and how we use them on our website.

## Use of personal information

Once you register or log in or submit information through our website we will know who you are and your activities on this website and information about you and/or your company may be recorded on our systems. There are a number of areas within the PCA Predict (formerly Postcode Anywhere) website which record personal data, including the: registration; billing; contact; invoice; and account sections. The information requested within these sections is standard and includes name, address, phone number and email details and is collected for the purposes of: 

  * administering your account (this will therefore include: registering your account; processing any orders which you make; communicating with you on any matter relating to the conduct of your account; and the provision of our services to you in general);
  * internal record keeping;
  * product and service development;
  * developing our website;
  * answering your queries or complaints;
  * market research; and
  * marketing our own products and services to you.

We would like to provide you with information about special features of our website, and/or PCA's products and services, and other information which we think you may find interesting. We may send you such information by post, push notification, email and/or telephone unless you have asked us not to do so. If you are a customer of ours or you have previously asked us for information on our products and services, we may send you information by email. However, in every marketing email message we send you we will give you the opportunity to unsubscribe from our mailings altogether. We do not provide your personal information to external organisations (i.e. outside of PCA for their own marketing purposes without your explicit consent). If at any time you do not want your information used for direct marketing purposes please contact us at support@pcapredict.com or on +44 1905 888 550 and if you decide that you no longer wish to receive marketing emails from us, please either follow the unsubscribe link in one of our marketing email messages or contact us at support@pcapredict.com or on +44 1905 888 550. Where we are undertaking any services in collaboration with a third party (this will be clear from either the branding or notices on the website), then we may be required in order to provide the respective services, to share your account details with such third party in order to administrate the account (in a similar manner as mentioned above) and provide the respective services.

We will also need to share details about your use of our services with our data licensors and authorised resellers, with such details including the number of users and volume of transactions, so that appropriate licence fees and other payments can be calculated. We may also use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us develop the website and our services. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify any individual. 

## Email addresses

We collect email addresses for 3 main purposes:

  * Email is our preferred means of communication, and will be used to notify our customers of developments within the PCA Predict services.
  * We use email to administer your account, for example, by alerting you when your account balance reaches a given level.
  * The email address on registration will be used to authenticate users who have forgotten passwords or user account IDs.

## Where We Process Your Personal Data

Although we process your data within the European Economic Area ("EEA"), owing to the global nature of the Internet infrastructure, the information you provide may be transferred in transit to other countries outside the EEA that do not have similar protections in place as the EEA regarding your data and its use as set out in this policy. By submitting your information you consent to such transfers outside the EEA. Your personal information may be shared with other companies within the PCA group of companies based within or outside of the UK. We may also have third party companies providing hosting services for us. Such third party companies will act as our subcontractors, and they would hold your data for such hosting purposes only. Such subcontractors will not be provided with any permission for any other use or disclosure of your data. We will also ensure that we have reasonable safeguards in place with regard to any of our subcontractors, with regard to data retention and security. Please bear in mind that the countries to which your personal data is sent may have a different standard of data protection than the UK. 

## Compliance & Confidentiality

Our company complies with its obligations under the applicable data protection legislation in England. It will also take reasonable care to prevent any unauthorised access to your personal data. Our employees and contractors have been made aware of their responsibility to keep your information confidential. 

## Security

As you will probably be aware, the internet is not a secure medium. However we have put in place various security procedures by way of reasonable measures to protect your information. We consider the security of your personal data and the details of any transactions you make to be a matter of the highest priority. Your account information is protected by your account code and password which you should keep safe at all times. In addition to your password, we generate keys which are used to authenticate your account against our servers when you are querying the database. Keys are a randomly generated and unique set of letters and numbers. If you feel that there has been a breach in the security on your licence please contact us on +44 1905 888 550 or by email at security@pcapredict.co.uk. 

## Purchasing

When you place an order with us, we use a secure server. Any data you provide to us, is encrypted using a 'Secure Socket Layer' (SSL) session. SSL is an industry standard and is a widely used measure to guard against Internet messages being intercepted. You should be aware, however, that older browsers cannot use SSL. To be sure, you will need Netscape version 4.05 or above, Microsoft Internet Explorer version 4 or above, or any similar generation browser (e.g. Firefox, Opera). Although your account can be set up to make repeat purchases to automatically top-up your account by credit card, we do not actually store credit card details. We only hold the last 4 digits of your card, the card holder name and a reference to the last transaction made on that card from us. It is the transaction reference that is used to make repeat purchases and this can only be used between ourselves and our payment service provider, SecureTrading. 

## Protecting your data

Over and above what our company does to protect your privacy and security, we would advise you to adopt the following additional measures:

  * Choose a password you can remember but others will not guess.
  * Change your password regularly, and if you do write it down, keep it somewhere safe and secure.
  * Do not activate Autocomplete (Internet Explorer) or any similar feature.
  * Do not allow your internet browser to 'remember' passwords.
  * When you have finished your session on our website we recommend that you close your browser, so any history of the session is cleared. As a further security measure our website will automatically shut down your session if it is not used for more than 20 minutes.
  * Clear any 'cache' so there is no record of any transactions left on screen - all major web browsers let you do this.

## Use of cookies

Our website creates a cookie every time you access the website. We may also place cookies (or similar tags) on the websites of our customer(s). Read more about [our use of cookies and see Disabling/Enabling Cookies below](http://www.pcapredict.com/cookies/?__hstc=210931082.11771deb38c53ceb9ed64e52df732ddc.1522155831162.1522155831162.1522245170705.2&__hssc=210931082.2.1522245170705&__hsfp=1962557905). 

## Use of Web Beacons

Some of our web pages may contain electronic images known as web beacons (sometimes known as clear gifs) that allow us to count users who have visited these pages. Web beacons collect only limited information which includes a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides. We may also carry web beacons placed by third party advertisers. These beacons do not carry any personally identifiable information and are only used to track the effectiveness of a particular campaign.

## Third Party Advertising

We may use a third party to serve advertisements on our site. Cookies may be associated with these advertisements to enable the advertiser to track the number of anonymous users responding to the campaign. We do not have access to or control of cookies placed by third parties. Disabling/Enabling Cookies If you register with our website, or if you continue to use this website, you agree to our use of cookies. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser or using the link in our cookies policy [[here]](http://www.pcapredict.com/cookies/?__hstc=210931082.11771deb38c53ceb9ed64e52df732ddc.1522155831162.1522155831162.1522245170705.2&__hssc=210931082.2.1522245170705&__hsfp=1962557905). However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our website if cookies are disabled. In order to block or delete cookies, select the “Help” entry under the ""Help" menu of your internet browser and type in ""delete cookies" or "block cookies" to find a step by step process of how to undertake such actions. 

## Third party sites

Third party Internet sites that hotlink to PCA Predict are not covered by our Privacy and Security policy. PCA Predict accepts no responsibility or liability for these sites.

## Sale of business

If this business is sold or integrated with another business, your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers, and will be passed on to the new owners of the business. You will be informed of any change in ownership in our business.

## Updating your details

If any of the information that you have provided to us changes, for example if you change your e-mail address, name or other details, please let us know the correct details by sending an e-mail to accounts@pcapredict.co.uk.

## Your consent

By submitting your information, you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it. We may also e-mail you, should we make any changes to the way in which we use your information so that you may consent to our use of your information in that way. Continued use of the service will signify that you agree to any such changes, and that you have consented to such use of your information.

## Right of access to your information & how to contact us

When you visit our website, you have direct control over information in your personal profile. If you want to know exactly what personal information we hold on you, you can obtain it. If the information held is found to be inaccurate, we will make the necessary amendments and confirm to you that these have been made. Please write to the following address, enclosing a cheque for the administration fee of £10 (or if higher, such other fee as stipulated by statute or the Office of the Information Commissioner from time) made payable to GB Group plc, pursuant to the terms of the Data Protection Act: 

IT Director,  
GB Group plc (PCA Predict),  
Waterside,  
Basin Road,  
WORCESTER,  
WR5 3DA.  

If you would like to contact us with any other queries or comments, then either [send an email here](http://www.pcapredict.com/cookies/?__hstc=210931082.11771deb38c53ceb9ed64e52df732ddc.1522155831162.1522155831162.1522245170705.2&__hssc=210931082.2.1522245170705&__hsfp=1962557905) or please write to the Customer Service Department at the above address.
